He gave it to one of his colleagues, not this guy, because he swore that he was not going to stamp the passport.
So he gave it to one guy that he should stamp it, and I said, okay, however, I still have a question.
I want to know, is there any law or any tariff, something about stamping the passport when people are equalized?
I want to know. He said, come, he took me to his office up there.
There's nothing. There's nothing like that. There's absolutely nothing.
What is happening is that sometimes they would even ask for ink to stamp these things, and they have to pay from their pocket.
And sometimes they are even tired of all these things, because they would ask the federal government.
They would bring these things six months after the request, you know, and they have to do something about it.
So at the end of the day, they are like, you don't know, if people can contribute on doing this kind of thing, yes, it's not that different.
I say, oh, that's something. Seriously. See, I park my car here, I always park it here.
The boys, when I go in circles, they come back, they are here, they are washing my car.
The women wash it before I even ask, they know me now, I give them 1000, 2000.
Some of the people said, you know, immigration guys, I become friendly with them.
We'll go and have our play somewhere, and we'll eat peppers, we'll get everything, you know.
I don't have any problem with spending money or giving money for this kind of thing.
But I think it has to go with, you know, people have to be cultures.
Because the way he is doing it is like an obligation.
And to me, this is a frustrating.
And I wonder if this is what they are doing, they need to stop it, because it can't work.
Anyway, it is me, I'm passing there. This is always going to be a social fight,
because I will never pay for my passport and pass.