I love my country so much that, to me, I have to capitalise on my experience in the country
to see what I can bring into my country, not only in terms of governance, because I have
a lot of relations with people, but also in terms of business, business model.
There are things, I saw some things here that are working, I suggest I give the ideas to
some of my friends there.
And some have made it, it's good, it's working, by myself, I'm like, okay, so what I'm doing
here, you know, is media, media work and, you know, I will see continue to do that, but
myself, after everything, I'm also preparing myself to go back home, not really to stay
here for no longer, to go back home and capitalise on what I've had with relations, with everything
and anyone who wants to come to Nigeria, I'm always a resource person who can help him
fix up some things with some people, you know, give them that which is, so yes, I'm still
here, I'm still not leaving now.
And if very soon things are, okay, when I'm ready, but I'm preparing to settle back home.