I was just going for a while to know I used to go and relax.
Friday I would go and come back Monday morning early.
So I went and I packed my car and the burdens.
And I want to cross just with that.
My paper was not fine at that time.
So I just packed my car to give the paper.
So I saw the guy who was collecting money from people
with the paper stamping going.
So I looked at it.
When I came to him, he didn't even look at me.
He put his hand like that.
I now bend like that.
Sorry, sir.
This is my passport to stamp.
He said, hey.
So you're not seeing the order.
What they are doing, you know they see him.
OK, if you don't see him, go and sit down there.
You're not ready to go.
Don't worry.
And I went and sit down.
I sat and after like 15 minutes, I was like,
I was just looking at what is going on.
And I said, OK.
I saw now a guy who came.
They came with their boss.
The man took a long grocery, took the passport.
Maybe 30 or 50, I don't know, but it was 20.
And he went, he enters from the back of the office
of the guy, the immigration guy.
And he gave him money.
The man just took it.
He was just, you can see the paper, paper, paper, paper.
You're stamping, stamping, stamping.
I said, ah, good.
Good idea.
So me too, I went to the back.
And I waited.
When he finished, I entered.
I said, I'm sorry.
So he saw me, he said, what are you doing here?
I said, ah, OK.
I told you to, I have, because before that,
I went back again after 15 minutes to talk to him
that, OK, stamp my passport there.
Let me go.
He said, no, if I'm not paying, I should just leave it
and we'll go.
I said, OK, no, I can't pay.
I don't have the money to pay.
I said, you don't have the money.
Go ahead, sit down.
So I went back there.
So it is then now I saw the man now doing that.
And I came in.
I said, ah, he said, what's happening?
What are you doing in my office?
I said, no, OK.
I saw this man just enter here.
I see that you are doing it fast, fast, fast.
So I thought maybe when you enter here, they do it.
That's why I came.
He said, get out of my office.
I'm not signing.
I'll take your passport and go.
Just go.
I said, ah, no, I cannot do that.
I need to stamp.
Because when I'm going out, I need to know that I'm outside.
When I come in, I have to sign.
The man said, no, I should get out of his office now.
Before he gets there, I said, ah, OK.
I'm seriously going to stamp my passport.
I cannot go.
I will shoot at you.
He just stood up there.
And he said, if you annoy me now, I said, no, I cannot do it.
So I started shouting.
His colleague now, from there, now, he came now.
That, ah, what is happening?
What is happening?
The man is, he was, he holds now, like 60 something.
He said, ah, look at this young man.
He comes here in my office, he wants to embarrass me.
He's abusing me.
He's talking to me anyhow.
I said, ah, the police were there.
Even the organ came, Sam.
He's even, he passed four years ago.
Sam came down, the came, they were like, oh, I said, no,
me too, I said, no, I did not, you're my father's age.
I can't abuse you with the education I have.
I can never abuse you, I can never abuse you.
I told you to just stamp my passport.
He said, I should pay before I stamp.
I said, I cannot pay for that.
The organ said, OK, come, come, give me the passport.
I'm going to pass my two kids.