They are playing on the ignorance of people, you know.
Maybe it's because, okay, not probably because I'm a journalist,
but because I'm a lawyer in training.
So I know the rules, and I know that when you are in a coarser citizen,
there's nothing like payment, even to sign, you know,
to stamp your passport for you to cross, you know,
all those kinds of things, provided that you have all your documentations
and all your medical stuff, you're free to move.
But they are not doing that, you know, the borders.
And I always fight because I don't want to pay,
and I don't want not only me to pay,
but even people around me are telling them,
you are not paying, okay, sign this thing, let it go.
I became friends with a lot of them later because, you know,
they are like, ah, Mr. Jonathan, when I come, ah, bring this thing,
you know, they go, they go, they go, they go, they go.
Don't spoil it, well, you know, no, don't spoil it,
but I can't tell you, I'll tell you, go.
So...