Maybe Bukinabe did not distort me because I'm a Bukinabe, you understand?
But then I probably, they distort me very well, and I told them the same thing.
The man told me, he said, the generator that is there,
how do you want that the power, how do you want that the fuel, fueling it?
I said, how does it concern me?
It doesn't concern me, no.
Or if you want us to help you, take care of your generator,
just put the box there and put the paper, say,
help us to fuel our generator.
I will put money.
But here, I don't give you, even one cobalt, I don't give you.
Okay, so you have instances like that, a lot of things that happen.
How much was he asking for?
Pardon?
In the Republic, it's 500 safer, 500 safer.
At the border here, in Kotonu, it's in between 200 and 500.
They can ask you anything like that.
It depends on how they, but I don't know if they are stopped now,
because for a while, they are not traveling from the road there.
Because of that road, that's not good at all.
So, I don't know if they are.
And they have also modernized the, how do you call it,
the joint immigration point.
So, it is now, the last time I saw it, it was very nice.
They started doing something.
What was the last time you were there?
The last time I went there was,
almost two years ago, almost two years ago, I didn't go there.
Because I went, I actually went to Lomi,
not Kotonu, but I passed out in Lomi.
And it was, I think, around August, around August 2017.