Our people are ignorant of what is really normal, what to do, what not to do.
And me as a press man, okay, I will not just go and spoil your name or write something, I did not do that.
But at least, even them, I talk to them, okay, what you're doing is not right.
At least, just do your job normally.
If I'm happy, I can give you something for you to have a drink.
No problem, it's not an issue.
Don't force people, because I source to people also, they are standing.
They don't have money, or the small money they have to travel.
Sometimes the money is not even complete yet.
You will come and take after that money.
You force them to pay something.
No.
Okay, anyway, I had this one and say my border.
I had it at Lome, from Kotonu to Lome.
I had it at the border with the Kotonu, Lome people.
We fought seriously.
I even tried to go to meet the ogre.
And I would take the matter to the ministry.
I told them that day, before they do my paper.
So it is just like, it's normal for them.
Everywhere, even Benet.
Yes, Benet and Bukina Faso, not the same thing.