Let's say we can have a community, today I can, okay from the registration you have at the embassy
because all of them they're not even going there to register and all of them they're supposed to
do that but no. We are around let's say 600, 600 in Lagos here but you have some in some other
states like you have the consulate now is a new consulate and even this consulate we are the one
at the association that requested from our government to put a consulate here so that people
can go and do their papers there to understand because before we had to rely on the embassy
embassy which is in Labriger and there was just a liaison office economic liaison office here
that was helping with those things but we didn't hire we have to do it so that people can get the
right you know so you have six other states that vary from Lagos
you have ocean state, oil state
I'm getting those six in fact in the south here okay yeah
so it's basically the south west? Yes basically the south west
the east side they depend on Lagos and very soon we're going to have another one another
consulate that coming for the not people